<resources>
  <string name="app_name">Picture Quest</string>
  <string name="title_home">Story</string>
  <string name="title_dashboard">Choices</string>
  <string name="title_notifications">Camera</string>

  <!--  Input Request strings-->
  <string name="city_input_request">Please take a picture in a city setting.</string>
  <string name="nature_input_request">Please take a picture of a nature setting</string>
  <string name="indoors_input_request">Please take a picture indoors.</string>

  <string name="no_inputs_found">No possible inputs detected, please take another picture.</string>

  <!--  TODO finish Opening Storyline Strings-->
  <string name="opening_scene">Opening Scene</string>

  <!--   First Picture to 4 input options. Sign, Car, Building, plant-->
  <string name="sign_input_1">A sign in front of you says
    "Ashenmoore Village two miles" and points to the west. </string>
  <string name="car_input_1">You see an elderly man in tattered clothing driving a wagon,
    he says "Would you like to accompany me north, I hear there\'s bandits on the road."</string>
  <string name="building_input_1">To the east stands a tower belonging to the mage Duran,
    a dark blue light is shining through a window</string>
  <string name="plant_input_1">A tattered raven is perched in a tree nearby,
    he seems to be watching you intently.</string>

  <!--   What do you do, to be reused often!!!!! -->
  <string name="what_do_you_do">What do you do?</string>

  <!--  Decisions-->
  <string name="go_to_town">Follow the sign and walk to town.</string>
  <string name="get_on_wagon">Join the elderly man, and get onto the wagon. </string>
  <string name="go_to_tower">Investigate Duran\'s Tower.</string>
  <string name="go_to_raven">Walk towards the raven.</string>

  <!--  The branching paths begin!-->

  <string name="arrive_in_town">After cresting a steep hill, the town of Ashenmoore village sprawls
    before you, a man runs up to you panting heavily, "Please help me! My son has been poisoned,
    do you have any herbs that would help?</string>
  <!--  ^^    Nature input request ^^-->

  <string name="wagon_trip">The wagon creaks and sways as you travel along a well worn road
    through the forest, you hear a rustling in a bush ahead and a man wearing
    a hood jumps out from behind a bush. "Give me all of your gold and no one will be hurt.</string>
<!-- ^^ TODO figure out what request! Not sure what request  ^^ -->

  <string name="investigate_tower">As you approach the tower you notice the birds have stopped
    chirping near by and an erie hum has been getting louder. Suddenly a scream pierces through the
    air at the same time as you entering the tower.
    </string>
<!-- ^^  request indoor input  ^^ -->

  <string name="investigate_raven">The raven watches you every step of the way, as you get within a
    few feet a creaking voice calls out. "That is close enough for my comfort, we have been watching
    you, and believe you might be able to help us." The voice is coming from the raven!
    "Please follow me." as it flies into the forest. </string>
  <string name="to_camera">To Camera</string>
  <!--   ^^ Natue input request ^^-->

<!--TODO write out prompts first and make story arch-->


</resources>
